I don't think white women really understand how impactful they have been in the lives of so many
black people in negative ways. Like I can honestly tell you that I have had a lot of white women who
have been very positive in my life. However, because I have seen the multitude of ways that
they have been dangerous to others, I always keep a side eye. Yeah, to any white woman I meet,
I'm going to keep a side eye until proven otherwise. Because the reality is that I know
that certain white women treat me differently. Because even as I was a seventh grader, they were
saying, you're like black, but I like black, black. You know what I mean? They just decide like, oh,
I don't, I don't have to treat you that way. But it doesn't discount them treating other black people
the way that we've seen so many white women behave. And I don't think enough white women
really, really, really understand that. That y'all have managed to become weapons for other people's
destruction. The tears, the lies, all of it. It is very real. You saw it in that video with the nurse
and the black kids with the bike. It is not the first time. May Carolyn Bryant burn in hell.
If you know, you know.